klixion.com 2016-05-12

# Klixion · Innovative Autosurf Traffic Exchange

### Information we collect and how we use it

We may collect the following types of information:

Information you provide – When you sign up for a Klixion Account, we ask you for a few personal information (full name, email address, and desired password). For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. Please awknowledge that you will receive weekly newsletters and important messages from time to time from us via email you provided.

Cookies – When you visit Klixion, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving website rotations, and tracking user's traffic hits in and out.

Log information – When you access Klixion services via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

User communications – When you send email or other communications to Klixion, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services.

Third party vendors – Our website serves advertisements from third-party vendors who use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits. If you would like to opt-out of the use of PulseAudience cookie, please visit the ad exchange privacy page.

Other sites – This Privacy Policy applies to Klixion services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed in our "surf now!" rotations. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
